{
  "quizName": "a nu quiz",
  "randomize": true,
  "accountID": 1,
  "questions": [
      {
          "questionNum": 1,
          "question": "q1",
          "correctAnswer": "correct",
          "wrongAnswers": [
              "wrong",
              "nope",
              "bye"
          ]
      },
      {
          "questionNum": 2,
          "question": "q2",
          "correctAnswer": "correct2",
          "wrongAnswers": [
              "wrong2",
              "nope2",
              "bye2"
          ]
      },
      {
          "questionNum": 3,
          "question": "q3",
          "correctAnswer": "correct3",
          "wrongAnswers": [
              "wrong3",
              "nope3",
              "bye3"
          ]
      },
      {
          "questionNum": 4,
          "question": "q4",
          "correctAnswer": "correct4",
          "wrongAnswers": [
              "wrong4",
              "nope4",
              "bye4"
          ]
      },
      {
          "questionNum": 5,
          "question": "q5",
          "correctAnswer": "correct5",
          "wrongAnswers": [
              "wrong5",
              "nope5",
              "bye5"
          ]
      },
      {
          "questionNum": 6,
          "question": "q6",
          "correctAnswer": "correct6",
          "wrongAnswers": [
              "wrong6",
              "nope6",
              "bye6"
          ]
      },
      {
          "questionNum": 7,
          "question": "q7",
          "correctAnswer": "correct7",
          "wrongAnswers": [
              "wrong7",
              "nope7",
              "bye7"
          ]
      },
      {
          "questionNum": 8,
          "question": "q8",
          "correctAnswer": "correct8",
          "wrongAnswers": [
              "wrong8",
              "nope8",
              "bye8"
          ]
      },
      {
          "questionNum": 9,
          "question": "q9",
          "correctAnswer": "correct9",
          "wrongAnswers": [
              "wrong9",
              "nope9",
              "bye9"
          ]
      },
      {
          "questionNum": 10,
          "question": "q10",
          "correctAnswer": "correct10",
          "wrongAnswers": [
              "wrong10",
              "nope10",
              "bye10"
          ]
      }
  ]
}